A Guide to the Governor Terry McAuliffe, Policy Office, Records, 2002; 2006-2008; 2010-2018 (bulk 2014-2017)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Governor Terry McAuliffe, Policy Office, Records, 2002; 2006-2008; 2010-2018 (bulk 2014-2017)
The Library of Virginia
52177, 52782 and 53533
16.56 cu. ft. (24 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Office of the Governor, Patrick Henry Building, 1111 E. Broad Street, Richmond, Virginia, 23219, accession 52177 transferred on 12 January 2018 and accessioned on 17 January 2018; accession 52788 transferred and accessioned on 24 July 2019; accession 53533 transferred on 14 January 2022 and accessioned on 3 February 2022.
Historical Information
The Policy Office is a division of the Office of the Governor in the Executive Branch of Virginia state government. During Governor Terry McAuliffe's administration, the Policy Office was responsible for identifying emerging issues, implementing gubernatorial initiatives, and providing policy and political advice to the Governor. The Policy Office worked with the Cabinet and Administration to develop gubernatorial policies and conduct outreach to key stake holders. The Policy Office was responsible for managing the legislative process (preparing bills and legislative packages, legislative liaisons to the General Assembly and reviewing bills), assisting in the development of executive orders, reviewing budget requests, assisting the press office, scheduling office and chief of staff with policy background and analysis, and ensuring agency performance in implementing the administration's agenda.
Major policy initiatives focused on the economy, education, health care, natural resources, public safety and transportation. Some of the education initiatives included increased funding for pre-K and early childhood education, expanded workforce credentials and apprenticeship programs, and reforming the Standards of Learning (SOL) test. In health care, the Governor created the Task Force on Prescription Drugs and Heroin Abuse to address the heroin and opioid epidemics. The administration failed to expand Medicaid via the Affordable Care Act. Those efforts are included in this collection.
Scope and Content
The Governor Terry McAuliffe, Policy Office, Records are housed in 24 boxes. The collection is arranged into two (2) series. Series have been designated for: I. Legislative Guidance and Review; and II. Subject Files. These records include agreements, reports, correspondence, e-mail, memorandums, legal files, legislation, budget documents, agendas, handouts, talking points and meeting notes. These records document the work of the Policy Office during the McAuliffe administration and were created or collected between 2014-2018, though some documents in this collection pre-date this time period.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
I. Legislative Guidance and Review, 2002; 2013-2017
II. Subject Files, 2004; 2006-2008; 2010-2018 (bulk 2014-2017)
Related Material
OFFICE OF THE GOVERNOR-TERRY MCAULIFFE
The Governor Terry McAuliffe Administration Web Archive Collection, 2014-2018
The Executive Orders Digital Collection includes the executive orders and executive directives issued by Governor Terry McAuliffe.
LIVE WEBSITES
The Virginia General Assembly's Legislative Information System contains searchable databases for bills and resolutions from 1994 to the present and reports to the general assembly. It also includes links to the Code of Virginia, Virginia Administrative Code, Constitution of Virginia, Charters, Authorities, Compacts and Uncodified Acts.
The Virginia State Budget Portal provides information about Budget Bills, Budget Amendments, and Committee Reports related to the budget from 1996 to the present.
The Virginia Department of Planning and Budget assists the Governor's Office, General Assembly, and state agencies develop and implement the budget. The website contains information on Virginia's budget from 2000 to the present.
The Virginia Regulatory Townhall website is a source of information about proposed changes to Virginia's regulations, including a meetings calendar and board minutes. This site also facilitates public participation through online comment forums and an email notification service.
Contents List
- I. Legislative Guidance and Review, 2002; 2013-2017., Extent: 7.8 cubic feet (10 boxes). (Box 1-10)
  The Legislative Guidance and Review series is housed in 10 boxes and is arranged into two (2) subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Legislative Files (Session) and B. Legislative Files (Policy Analysts). These files include correspondence, legislative files, budget documents, along with subject files and supporting materials such as briefs, meeting records, presentations, and reports. This series documents the Governor's Policy Office guidance to, as well as the review by, Planning and Budget, Cabinet officials, Executive staff and agency heads in regards to legislative and budget matters.
  - Subseries I.A. Legislative Files (Session), 2010-2013., Extent: 5.7 cubic feet (7 boxes) (Box 1-7)
    This subseries is housed in 7 boxes. The original file order has been maintained. Each legislative file usually contains: the text of each bill including any amendments, bill tracking information, Governor's Summaries (prepared by the Division of Legislative Services), Legislative Action Summaries (for bills tabled, withdrawn or killed in committee), Governor's Policy Office Enrolled Bill Review Forms, Enrolled Bill Reviews (by Cabinet Secretary), Department of Planning and Budget Fiscal Impact Statements, and the Attorney General's Recommendations to the Governor (restricted for 75 years - attorney/client privilege).
    - 2014 Session
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 2 -499 (Box 1)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 500-1043 (Box 2)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 1044-1268; SB 2-298 (Box 3)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 302-673 (Box 4)
      - Reconvened Session (1 of 2), 2014. (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Reconvened Session (2 of 2), 2014. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 2015 Session
      - 2015 Legislative Proposals (Education and Human Resources) (1 of 3), 2014. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - 2015 Legislative Proposals (Education and Human Resources) (2 of 3), 2014. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - 2015 Legislative Proposals (Education and Human Resources) (3 of 3), 2014. (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - 2015 Legislative Proposals (Veterans and Defense Affairs), 2014. (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 324-1699, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 1700-1983, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 1984-2397, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 675-1040, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 1041-1466, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 1440, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 1662, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 1821, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 834, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 1025, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 1044, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 1349, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Reconvened Session, 2015. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 2016 Session
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 2-374, 2016. (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 378-756, 2016. (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 760-1391, 2016. (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 1-424, 2016. (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 425-781, 2016. (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Reconvened Session (1 of 2), 2016. (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Reconvened Session (2 of 2), 2016. (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - 2017 Session
      - 2017 Legislative Proposals (Education), 2016. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Governor's Legislative Package, 2017 Session of the General Assembly (1 of 2), 2016. (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Governor's Legislative Package, 2017 Session of the General Assembly (2 of 2), 2016. (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 1392-1659, 2017. (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 1661-1951, 2017. (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 1952-2216, 2017. (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, HB 2217-2477, 2017. (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 786-1118, 2017. (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 1122-1342, 2017. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Enrolled Bill Review, SB 1343-1594, 2017. (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Reconvened Session (1 of 3), 2017. (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Reconvened Session (2 of 3), 2017. (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Reconvened Session (3 of 3), 2017. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Subseries I.B. Legislative Files (Policy Analysts), 2002; 2013-2017., Extent: 2.18 cubic feet (3 boxes) (Box 8-10)
    This subseries is housed in three (e) boxes and is further divided by policy analyst. The legislative files documents the drafting and review of governor's bills, meetings with stake holders and legislative priorities from interest groups. The files may contain bill draft, talking points and correspondence regarding legislation.
    - I.B.1. Jennifer Wicker, Deputy Legislative Director, 2002; 2014-2015.
      - HB 30, Budget Bill, February 2014. (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Budget, May 2014. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - In the Absence of a Budget research, Compiled in 2014. (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - HB 1109 Veto Statement, April 2014. (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Virginia School Boards Association (VSBA), 2014-2015. (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Veto Session, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Education Legislation, January 2014. (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - HB 5008 (Rust) - Virginia Healthcare Independence Act, August-September 2014. (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Virginia First Cities (VFC), Proposed Legislative Program Review, 5 October 2014. (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - AFT/AFL-CIO 2015 Education Legislative Agenda, undated. (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Teach for America (TFA), March 2014. (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Tax Preferences, December 2014. (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Strategic Priorities, 2014. (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Virginia Education Association (VEA), 2015 Legislative Agenda, 15 October 2014. (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Virginia Board for People with Disabilities, 29 August 2014. (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Virginians for the Arts, 2014. (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Governor McAuliffe's FY 2015 Savings Plan, October 2014. (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Standards of Learning (SOL) Innovation Committee, June 2014; October-November 2014. (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Budget Conference Report (Education), 24 February 2015. (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Certificate of Public Need (COPN), December 2014. (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Meeting of Virginia House of Delegates, Health, Welfare and Institutions Committee (HWI), 18 September 2014. (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Enrolled Bill Review (EBR) (1 of 3), 2014 Session. (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Enrolled Bill Review (EBR) (2 of 3), 2014 Session. (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Enrolled Bill Review (EBR) (2 of 3), 2014 Session. (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Enrolled Bill Review (EBR), February-March 2015. (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Bill Review (Education) Notification on Academic Transcript, January-February 2015. (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Bill Review (Education) SCHEV: Sexual Misconduct Policies, January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Senate Budget Amendments, January 2014. (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - House Budget Amendments, January 2014. (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Bill Review (Education): HB 544 and HB 1123, January 2014. (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Bill Review (Education): HB 1115 Virtual Schools, January 2014. (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - 2015 General Assembly Session, Workforce Development Policy and Legislation, December 2014. (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Bill Review (Workforce) Change Composition of the Virginia Board of Workforce Development, January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Virginia Legislative Black Caucus, 2015 Legislative Agenda, 2015. (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Bill Review (HHR): SB 1029, SB 1069, SB 1123 and SB 1124, January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Attorney General's Recommendation to the Governor (2015 Session Bills) (RESTRICTED), December 2014. (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - 2015 Legislative Proposals, September 2014 and undated. (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - 2015 General Assembly Session, Health and Human Resources Bills, November-December 2014. (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - 2015 General Assembly Session, Health and Human Resources Bills, January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - 2015 General Assembly Session, Education Bills, October-December 2014. (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - SCHEV: Instate Tuition for Certain Students, December 2014-January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - Bill Review (Education): HB 1706 and SB 874, Expedited Retakes, January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - Bill Review (Workforce): HB 1822 and SB 1024, Apprenticeship, December 2014-January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - Bill Review: HB 1488, Virginia Land Conservation Foundation, January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - Bill Review: HB 1945 and SB 990, Leave-Domestic Violence, Sexual Assault, Stalking, January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - Bill Review (Workforce): HB 2033, Accountability in Workforce, December 2014-January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - Bill Review (Education), SB 992, Academic Credit for Military Training, January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Bill Review (Education), HB 1873 and SB 1320, Additional Accreditation, January 2015. (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Home school (Tebow bill), September 2014. (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - Governor's Budget, 28 February 2014. (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - Fort Monroe Authority Act, January 2014. (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - Enrolled Bill Review (EBR) Process, 12 February 2014. (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Equal Pay, 5 February 2014. (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Foster Care, Meeting with The Casey Family Program, 19 May 2014. (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Voices for Virginia's Children, 2015 Legislative Agenda, 2 December 2014. (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Alliance Group, December 2014. (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - University of Virginia (UVA), October 2014. (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - University of Richmond, Future of Richmond's Past, October 2014. (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Williams Mullen, Individual Income Tax Refunds, December 2014. (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Capital Results Meeting, 2 December 2014. (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - VECTRE Corporation Meeting, 2 December 2014. (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Eckert Seamans Meeting, 3 December 2014. (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Reed Smith Meeting, 8 December 2014. (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Troutman Sanders Meeting, 12 December 2014. (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Legislative Actions Summaries (LAS) for HB 1356, HB 1411 and SB 734, 6 January 2015. (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - 2015 Governor's Legislative Agenda, November-December 2014. (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Bill Status (select legislation), February 2015. (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Weekly Legislative Meetings, November 2014. (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - House Republican Education Agenda, 14 January 2014. (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - SB 5003 Governor McAuliffe's Bill Highlights, March 2014. (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Mental Health (New Laws), 4 June 2014. (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Bill Review (Education): HB 926, Behavioral Analysis, January-February 2014. (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Bill Review, HB 606 and SB 443, Judges, January-February 2014. (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Delegate Tag Greason, February 2014. (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Bill Review, SB 495 (Norment), Conservators of the Peace, February 2014. (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - 2015 Legislative Proposal for the Virginia Community College System, undated. (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - 2015 Legislative Process, July 2014. (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - 2015 Legislative Proposal for the Virginia Department of Environmental Quality (DEQ), 2014. (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Blueprints for Change: Criminal Justice Policy Issues in Virginia, 24 October 2014. (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Budget-Higher Education, August 2014. (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Budget-Education, K-12, February 2014. (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - HB 5010 (2014 Special Session), Budget Bill, September 2014. (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Budget Stuff, February 2014; September 2014. (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - 2015 Budget Savings, September-October 2014. (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - I.B.2. Rushawna Senior, Special Assistant for Policy, 2013-2014; 2017.
      - 2014 Legislative Patrons and Draft Language (Public Safety), November 2013-January 2014. (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Legislative files from Gail Jaspen, January-April 2014. (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Legislative Agenda, 2015 Session and 2017 Session, December 2014; 2017. (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - I.B.3. Connor Andrews, Policy Assistant, 2017.
      - 2018 Legislation, September 2017; undated. (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - I.B.4. Massey Whorley, Senior Policy Advisor, 2017.
      - Memos/Letters Sent to the Governor's Office, January-November 2017. (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - I.B.5. Suzanne Gore, Policy Advisor, 2016-2017.
      - Bill Review (Health and Human Resources Legislation) (1 of 2), 2016-2017. (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Bill Review (Health and Human Resources Legislation) (2 of 2), 2017. (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - I.B.6. Jennie Moline O'Holleran, Senior Policy Advisor to the Governor/Policy Director, 2014-2017.
      - 2015 Legislative Proposals, 2014. (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - 2016 Legislative Proposals (1 of 3), 2015-2016. (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - 2016 Legislative Proposals (2 of 3), 2015-2016. (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - 2016 Legislative Proposals (3 of 3), 2015. (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Women's Health Amendment Proposals, September 2016. (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Budget (2017 Session), September-October 2016. (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - 2017 Legislative Proposals (1 of 2), 2016. (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - 2017 Legislative Proposals (2 of 2), 2016. (Box 9, Folder 46)
      - Bill Review (Wireless/Broadband), HB 2916/SB 1282, January-February 2017. (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - Bill Review (Wireless/Broadband), HB 2108, January-February 2017. (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - 2018-2020 Budget Requests, 2017. (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - 2018 Legislative Proposals, 2017. (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - 2018 Legislative Proposals, Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2017. (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - 2018 Legislative Proposals, Secretary of Technology, 2017. (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - Correspondence, 2017. (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - I.B.7. Margaret Chambers, Special Assistant, 2016-2017.
      - Local Government and School District Consolidation Study, 2016. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - 2017 Legislative Proposals, Education, 2016. (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Foster Care Tuition Grant, 7 November 2016. (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Virtual Schools, 7 November 2016. (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Virginia Guaranteed Assistance Program (VGAP), 7 November 2016. (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - 2017 Legislative Session Planning Meeting, 30 November 2016. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Legislative Meeting Agendas, 13, 23, 27 January 2017. (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Legislative Session Notes, January 2017. (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Bill Review, HB 401, Student Debt, January 2017. (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - 2017 Session Bill Tracking, February 2017. (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Letters Sent to the Governor's Office, February-March 2017. (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Enrolled Bills for Governor's Signature, Transmittal Memorandums, February-April 2017. (Box 10, Folder 12)
- II. Subject Files, 2004; 2006-2008; 2010-2018 (bulk 2014-2017)., Extent: 8.68 cubic feet (14 boxes). (Box 11-24)
  The Subject Files series is housed in 14 boxes and is arranged into eleven (11) subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Anna Healy James, Policy Office Director; B. Jennifer Wicker, Deputy Legislative Director; C. Jennie Moline O'Holleran, Senior Policy Advisor to the Governor/Policy Director; D. Jay Swanson, Deputy Policy Director; E. Suzanne Gore, Policy Advisor; F. Massey Whorley, Senior Policy Advisor; G. Matt West, Policy Assistant; H. Margaret Chambers, Special Assistant for Policy; I. Erik Johnston, Deputy Policy Director; J. Connor Andrews, Policy Assistant; and K. Miscellaneous. These files include correspondence, memorandums, email, legislative files, budget documents, briefs, meeting records, presentations, reports, talking points, executive orders, and notes. This series documents the work of individual members of the Policy Office and the McAuliffe administration's policy initiatives. Those initiatives include, but are not limited to: Medicaid expansion, education, early childhood education, workforce development, Governor's Task Force on Prescription Drugs and Heroin Abuse, energy policy, and transportation.
  - Subseries II.A. Anna Healy James, Policy Office Director, 2004; 2006-2007; 2010-2016., Extent: 1.7 cubic feet (3 boxes) (Box 11-13)
    This subseries is housed in 3 boxes and arranged alphabetically by subject. On 6 January 2014, Governor-elect Terry McAuliffe appointed Anna Healy James as Policy Office Director. In addition to overseeing the Policy Office, James' policy areas included education, energy, finance, health and human resources, Medicaid expansion, and taxation. James previously served as Special Assistant to Governor Mark Warner for policy, where she established and oversaw the Governor's Healthy Virginians initiative as well as advised the Governor on issues such as teacher quality, K-12 education, healthcare and higher education. Prior to her appointment to the McAuliffe administration, James served as Manager for State Government Affairs for Troutman Sanders Strategies. James left the McAuliffe administration in September 2016.
    - 111d (EPA's Proposed Clean Power Plan to Regulate CO2 from Existing Electric Generating Units, 26 June 2014. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Abortion Clinic Regulations, 2015-2016. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Administration Health Plan, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - August 1st Speech, August 2014. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Bio, undated. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Budget Briefings, 16 September 2014. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Center Virginia Health Services, undated. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - CGI, 2011-2012; 2014. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Clean Power Plan Finalization Roll Out: Virginia, 11 August 2015. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 2015-2016. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Council on Virginia's Future, April 2015. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Cyber, undated. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Day Care, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Delivery System Reform Incentive Payments (DSRIP), 2014. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Dominion Power, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Dominion Power, 2014-2016. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Education, 2015. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - eHHR Program, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Ethics, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Executive Directive 2 (2014) Evaluation of Major Information Technology and Service Contracts in State Government, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Finance, 2013-2014. (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - First Lady of Virginia, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Gift Cards, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - GO Virginia, undated. (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Governor McAuliffe's Latino Roundtable, 3 September 2014. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates (GACRE), 2014-2015. (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Governor's Opportunity Fund, 2014. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Health and Human Resources Transition Working Group, December 2013. (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Healthcare, 2014; 2016. (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Healthy VA, 2010; 2012; 2014. (Box 11, Folder 30)